Nicholas Weber

Front-End Web Developer & UX Designer

nikkoweber@live.com · (612)-295-2668 · nikkoweber.com

Professional Summary

More than three years of experience as both a designer and developer of corporate websites. Have numerous achievements under my belt, including the complete design and development of a corporate website (100+ pages including an eCommerce system) from scratch. Experience with both traditional web markup and content management systems; able to adaptably use both with proficiency.

Education

Capella University (2018-2019)

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Minor in Web Application Development

Experience

Web Developer Intern

Lube-Tech, Golden Valley, MN / Jan 2016 - Feb 2020

- · Was paid to learn WordPress fundamentals and custom theming
- Designed the company website (100+ pages) from scratch
- Developed the new company website in Angular
- Designed and implemented the UI for the eCommerce system
- · Made modifications and additions to the website over time

Web Developer

TravelNet Solutions, Cottage Grove, MN / Feb 2020 - Mar 2020

- Developed web content in the WordPress theme Avada
- Implemented web content for various clients
- · Created modifications to the existing web content
- Laid off due to COVID-19's impact on the hospitality industry

Professional Skills

- Front-end web development
- User experience design
- Responsive design
- Responsive development
- Angular 2+
- Angular Material
- WordPress
- Avada
- JavaScript
- JavaScript DOM manipulation
- Image manipulation
- Prototyping
- HTML5
- CSS3
- SASS
- BootStrap